the top five reasons why you should
consider buying tvs
raider 125 if you are in the market
looking for an 125 cc with a good budget
and the first reason definitely has to
be the looks update supposed to look
temporary
this looks quite awesome
i mean just really like awesome yeah
but in this range which it belongs to
the
commuter range so this is the power he
produced he had 11.2 bhp
and coming up to the third point is
and you can hear the exhaust
exhaust caffeine
which you can see is 57.
around considering it's a 125 sporty
series 40 commuter bike
around upcoming
5758 and something those kind of bikes
bought the last power producer
then definitely you can go for this if
your budget is a little bit tighter then
go for the drum bag variant which should
be around at one like two thousand
something like that and this the disk
back variant this costs around one like
nine thousand
on this tvs radio then do subscribe to
my channel i will be giving you a
ownership review at 1500 kilometers
japanese kilometers
or plus uh owner experience
here
build quality how to maintain it all
this thank you so much